teagames.com 2005-03-05

# Teagames.com - Privacy Policy

## 1\. About this web site

1.1  This web site is an online service of David Thorburn (referred to below as "David Thorburn"). David Thorburn's full contact details are below.

1.2  This Privacy Policy applies to all and any use of this web site.

1.3  Since David Thorburn is principally aiming this site web site at the UK and EU markets, David Thorburn cannot guarantee that it accords with local laws of any other countries (though David Thorburn will try to make sure it does).

1.4  In addition to this Privacy Policy please read the [Terms of Use](http://www.teagames.com/index.php?page=terms) before using this web site.

## 2\. Privacy Policy Statement

2.1  David Thorburn makes a commitment to protecting your privacy and promises only to use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Electronic Commerce (EC Directive) Regulations 2002 ("E-Commerce Directive") and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 ("E-Communications Regulations").

2.2  David Thorburn collects information for two reasons - to enable David Thorburn to process your requirements and to provide you with an up to date, efficient, and reliable gaming service.

2.3  David Thorburn may ask you to submit personal data to the web site (for example your name, email address or contact details) to enable David Thorburn to provide you with the services available through the web site. This information will be kept securely in accordance with David Thorburn's internal security policy and may be used, stored and processed to improve the operation, administration and development of the web site as well as for marketing, advertising and promotional purposes but only in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws.

2.4  Once you have contacted David Thorburn and used David Thorburn's services, you have a choice on whether or not you want David Thorburn to contact you about future games and new items. David Thorburn will not bombard you with emails, but David Thorburn would like to keep you informed of the developments on this web site.

2.5  From time to time David Thorburn may share this data with other reputable companies within the European Union who may contact you about services similar to those on this web site.

2.6  Where requested please check the relevant box marked:

[  ] "please send me further information" if you wish to receive information regarding this web site or David Thorburn's games and services. If you do not check the box then David Thorburn will not use your data in that way and will not email you with information.

[  ] "please pass on this data to reputable third parties whom may have information and services of interest for me" if you want David Thorburn to pass the information on to third parties;

If you do not check the box then David Thorburn will not pass your data in that way.

2.7  David Thorburn will not transfer your information out of the EEA (European Economic Area) under any circumstances.

## 3\. Cookies

3.1  In order to improve David Thorburn's service and games David Thorburn uses a device known as a 'cookie'. Cookies are a means by which information relating to your Internet activity (such as whether you have visited www.teagames.com before) is recorded and used by David Thorburn to improve this web site and the games and services available to you.

3.2  If you do not wish for David Thorburn to use cookies when you use www.teagames.com please adjust your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. Your computer's help file should tell you how to do this. For example:

Internet Explorer version 4.0 and up:

Pull Down Tools Menu and click on Internet Options...  
Click on Privacy tab  
Choose between the range of "Accept All cookies" to "Block All Cookies".  
Medium Privacy is the default in that range.

Netscape version 4.08 and up:

Pull down Edit menu and click on Preferences.  
Click on Advanced category  
Under Cookies section click on the "Disable cookies" radio button  
You may also choose to be less restrictive, but then check the "Warn me before accepting a cookie" check box.  
Click on the OK button

Alternatively you can contact David Thorburn [here](http://www.teagames.com/index.php?page=contact).

WARNING: IF YOU CHOOSE TO DISABLE COOKIES THE GAMES AND SERVICES ON THIS WEBSITE WILL NOT WORK.
